export default data1 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "What is the Home Secretary responsible for?",
        options: ["Health", "Defence", "Education", "Policing"],
        correct_option: "Policing"
    },
    {
        id: "q2",
        question: "St Helena is a British overseas territory and it is part of the United Kingdom.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
    {
        id: "q3",
        question: "Several Church of England bishops sit in the House of Lords.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
    {
        id: "q4",
        question: "Which Scottish city is known as the home of golf?",
        options: ["Dundee", "Edinburgh", "Aberdeen", "St Andrews"],
        correct_option: "St Andrews"
    },
    {
        id: "q5",
        question: "When did Ireland become a republic?",
        options: ["1925", "1939", "1949", "1927"],
        correct_option: "1949"
    },
    {
        id: "q6",
        question: "Where did the first farmers come from?",
        options: ["South-west Europe", "South-east Europe", "North-east America", "North-west Asia"],
        correct_option: "South-east Europe"
    },
    {
        id: "q7",
        question: "The National Anthem ‘God save the queen’ can only be played in the presence of the Queen.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
    {
        id: "q8",
        question: "Who became Prime Minister and was an inspirational leader to the British people during WWII?",
        options: ["Winston Churchill", "Clement Attlee", "Margaret Thatcher", "Sir Robert Walpole"],
        correct_option: "Winston Churchill"
    },
    {
        id: "q9",
        question: "What is the title of the Queen’s eldest son, Prince Charles?",
        options: ["Prince of Kent", "Prince of Wales", "Prince of Hanover", "Prince of Brunswick"],
        correct_option: "Prince of Wales"
    },
    {
        id: "q10",
        question: "When was the Magna Carta created?",
        options: ["1514", "1215", "1415", "1314"],
        correct_option: "1215"
    },
    {
        id: "q11",
        question: "Which of the following plays was written by William Shakespeare?",
        options: ["Pride and Prejudice", "A Midsummer Night’s dream", "Sense and Sensibility", "Great Expectations"],
        correct_option: "A Midsummer Night’s dream"
    },
    {
        id: "q12",
        question: "How many members does a jury have in England, Wales and Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["9", "12", "15", "20"],
        correct_option: "12"
    },
    {
        id: "q13",
        question: "St Patrick’s day is a public holiday in Northern Ireland.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
    {
        id: "q14",
        question: "Which was the last successful foreign invasion of England that took place in 1066?",
        options: ["The Viking invasion", "The Anglo-Saxon Conquest", "The Roman invasion", "The Norman Conquest"],
        correct_option: "The Norman Conquest"
    },
    {
        id: "q15",
        question: "Where are the Crown Jewels kept?",
        options: ["At the House of Commons", "At the Tower of London", "At Buckingham Palace", "At Windsor Castle"],
        correct_option: "At the Tower of London"
    },
    {
        id: "q16",
        question: "Which sport can be traced back to the 15th century in Scotland?",
        options: ["Golf", "Tennis", "Football", "Rugby"],
        correct_option: "Golf"
    },
    {
        id: "q17",
        question: "Who was the first person in England to print books using a printing press?",
        options: ["William Shakespeare", "John Barbour", "Geoffrey Chaucer", "William Caxton"],
        correct_option: "William Caxton"
    },
    {
        id: "q18",
        question: "Which court deals with minor criminal cases in England, Wales and Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["High Court", "Justice of the Peace Court", "Magistrates’ Court", "Crown Court"],
        correct_option: "Magistrates’ Court"
    },
    {
        id: "q19",
        question: "What did the Scottish John Logie Baird develop?",
        options: ["Television", "Radar", "Personal computer", "Radio"],
        correct_option: "Television"
    },
    {
        id: "q20",
        question: "Where is Loch Lomond and the Trossachs National Park located?",
        options: ["East of Wales", "West of Wales", "West of Scotland", "East of Scotland"],
        correct_option: "West of Scotland"
    },
    {
        id: "q21",
        question: "What is the name of the best preserved prehistoric village in northern Europe and which origin traces back to the Stone Age?",
        options: ["Maiden", "Skara Brae", "Stonehenge", "Bayeux"],
        correct_option: "Skara Brae"
    },
    {
        id: "q22",
        question: "When was the National Trust founded?",
        options: ["1890", "1895", "1980", "1990"],
        correct_option: "1895"
    },
    {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Elizabeth I was the younger daughter of which King?",
        options: ["James I", "William the Great", "Henry VII", "Henry VIII"],
        correct_option: "Henry VIII"
    },
    {
        id: "q24",
        question: "Which of the following operas was written by Gilbert and Sullivan?",
        options: ["The Phantom of the Opera", "The Mikado", "The Mousetrap", "Cats"],
        correct_option: "The Mikado"
    }
]